http://library.cuesta.cc.ca.us/about/info/security_policy.html

Skip to ContentSkip to Top Navigation Skip to Main Navigation Skip to Secondary Navigation Skip to Footer Links
Secondary NavigationToggle navigationInfo about Cuesta
Relationship to Cal PolyFast Facts
Security and Personal Privacy
Advancing Equity, Diversity, and Inclusion
21 Day Racial Equity & Social Justice ChallengeEquity Professional Development Resources
Cuesta History
Cuesta History
Hollister Adobe
Hollister AdobeDonate to the Hollister Adobe FundFriends of the Adobe
Transaction Security
When you are performing credit card transactions on the Cuesta College Web Site, you
are utilizing our secure server, which encrypts all of your personal information,
including name, address, and credit card number. Encryption ensures that no one can
access or use your personal information. With encryption the information cannot be
read as it travels over the Internet. Additionally, credit card numbers are used only
for payment processing and are not retained for other purposes. We collect only the
information required to process orders. When your credit card information is transmitted
to our Merchant Service for validation, it is encrypted and only our Merchant Service
has the key that will unencrypt that data. Please keep in mind that e-mail does not
use SSL encryption technology and we advise against sending credit card information
to us via e-mail. We will not be responsible for the confidentiality of any personal
or credit card information transmitted via e-mail.
Our 128-bit encryption is implemented on SSL 3.0 with a certificate from Thawte and
IPSCA. SSL encryption is active in all areas where credit card transaction information
is requested. You can check to see that you have entered an SSL-active area by looking
on the bottom of your screen. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending
on your browser), you will know that SSL technology is in place and ready to encrypt
your information. How to check if you are on a secure page? Look up at your address
line at the top of your browser page for the (http://). You will notice in the address
line, that there is an (https://) rather than an (http://). The (s) indicates that
you are on a secure page. Also, you'll see a key or a closed lock icon depending on
your browser. These symbols tell you that any information you send to us will be "scrambled"
using SSL technology. SSL uses "Public-Key Encryption" to exchange a session key between
you and our server. This session key is used to encrypt (or scramble) your transaction
twice - when it is sent and when it is received. If you are using a security-enabled
browser, your information is secure. Please note that in some systems, such as myCuesta
registration and payment screens, the secure window is wrapped in a frame and therefore
the security symbols may not necessarily appear. These pages are still using SSL technology,
and your protection is top priority.
How we collect information
When you visit our Web pages or utilize transaction features on our site, Cuesta College's
web servers automatically collect information about you. Some information is detected
electronically, and is collected without your direct input. Other information may
be voluntarily provided by you as you place an order, fill out forms (personal information,
meeting or course registration, guest book, parking registration, etc.), or send us
e-mail.
Information you involuntarily provide
When you visit Cuesta's web site, our server automatically logs information about
your visit:
Your Internet Provider (IP) address
We use this information to learn about our visitors as a group - not about you as an individual. This information helps us identify overall usage patterns and trends on the site.
Additionally, we may use this information for any of the following purposes:
Identify how much traffic various areas of the site receive
Identify peak and off-usage times and days. (This helps us determine when to schedule
site maintenance) Identify which other Web Sites send visitors to our site
Determine the number of visitors from various locations
Optimize the site for common browsers used to access the site
The above information is used by software programs on our Web Site to create summary
statistics which allow us to assess the number of visitors to the different sections
of our site, identify what information is of most and least interest, determine technical
design specifications, monitor system performance, and help us make our site more
useful to visitors.
Information you voluntarily provide via interactive web based forms
There are several transaction sites on the Cuesta College web site that allow users
to send money to the college. These transactions involve submission of some kind of
electronic form. When you use online (or traditional printed) forms, you voluntarily
provide Cuesta College with the following information:
Additional information may be gathered, depending on the nature of the form. This
information may include, but not be limited to, the following:
When you send us e-mail and request a response, we use the e-mail address you have
provided to respond to your inquiry. We may periodically log the nature of these e-mail
requests to help us analyze visitor interests overall and identify areas for improvement
on the site.
You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, (for example your
mailing address) in an electronic mail message requesting that information be mailed
to you. Information collected in this manner is used solely for responding to requests
for information or records. We may forward your E-mail to other Cuesta employees who
are better able to respond to you.
If you are using our my.cuesta.edu email system, the privacy policy governing Gmail
may be found here.
Use of "cookies"
Cookies are small text files placed in your computer system to track certain pieces
of information about your browser and your interaction with a web site. Cuesta College
uses cookies for a variety of technology applications on our site to verify your credentials
and keep you logged into secure areas, but we do not collect any data from cookies
other than what is needed to diagnose or maintain our systems.
Third-party use of information
Cuesta College will not sell, trade, rent or disclose any personal information that
you provide to us on-line to third parties unless specifically noted. Student email
systems may be exempt from this provision for security purposes. All information will
be kept private and confidential.
External Sites
This site contains links to other external sites. Cuesta College is not responsible
for the privacy practices, content or availability of any linked, external Web sites.
Thank you for taking the time to educate yourself about the ways in which Cuesta College
collects, uses, and stores the information that you provide. Please revisit this site
on occasion to make sure that you have viewed the most recent version of the privacy
policy and security statement. Cuesta College reserves the right to change any of
the information listed on this document and will notify users of any changes by posting
the new version of this document to the site at the Security Statement & Privacy Policy
link.
Info about Cuesta
Relationship to Cal PolyFast Facts
Security and Personal Privacy
Advancing Equity, Diversity, and Inclusion
21 Day Racial Equity & Social Justice ChallengeEquity Professional Development Resources
Cuesta History
Cuesta History
Hollister Adobe
Hollister AdobeDonate to the Hollister Adobe FundFriends of the Adobe
Featured NewsView All News »
Trustees Approve Censure Resolution
SLO United Concert Brings Together 18 Local Choral Groups for Virtual Performances
Cuesta College Celebrates Class of 2020
Featured EventsView All Events »
Campus MapsStay well Cuesta! Find open buildings, temperature kiosks, and available bathrooms
on both campuses.
Learn more about this »
© 2020 Cuesta College
